Ralph halabi

ralphhalabi22@gmail.com 961 76 390 457 Beirut

Summary

Self-taught and ambitious, I am a front-end web developer focused on expanding my skills and experience. With a passion for creating user-friendly, engaging websites, I am constantly exploring new technologies and approaches to stay at the forefront of web development.

Experience

Front end Web Developer

Digital Splash 05/2023 - Present

In my role as the sole Front End Web Developer at Digital Splash, I am responsible for the complete spectrum of front-end development tasks. This includes problem-solving, design conceptualization, coding, and implementation of custom websites from inception to completion. I handle all aspects of client interaction, gathering requirements, and translating them into tangible solutions. Additionally, I am proficient in React TypeScript, and I take pride in my ability to deliver high-quality, responsive, and mobile-friendly websites that seamlessly operate across all devices. This role has not only honed my technical skills but has also allowed me to thrive in a dynamic problem-solving environment, contributing significantly to my professional growth.

Freelance Web Developer

Freelance 02/2022 - Present

As a freehand website developer, I have been responsible for designing, coding, and implementing custom websites from the ground up. My role has involved working with clients to gather requirements, creating wireframes and mockups to visualize the design, and writing clean, valid code to bring the designs to life.

I have experience with a variety of programming languages, including HTML, CSS, and JavaScript including WordPress and Shopify and am skilled at creating responsive, mobile-friendly websites that work seamlessly across all devices. I take pride in delivering high-quality work and strive to exceed my clients' expectations

Shift leader

Crepaway • jounieh 02/2017 - 12/2022

- Manage daily operations
- Oversee multiple personnel
- · Help with onboarding and training
- · Overseeing the guest management and service quality
- Knowledge of costs associated with restaurant operations
- · Aware of competition review

Skills

HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, React.js, WordPress, Shopify, Time management, Communication skills

Education

BT: Baccalaureate Technique Administration

institue mon segnieur cortbawi